那么...
So...
你们竟然没有一个人回复说参加
couldn't help but notice none of you RSVP'd
我的杀人推理解密聚会
to my murder mystery dinner party.
哦 对
Oh, yeah.
我们打算回复你的
We were meaning to do that.
不 因为聚会是在一个礼拜前的
No, you weren't because it was a week ago
而且一个人都没来!
and nobody came!
所以 那个冷落死者Koothrappali
So, if you want to solve the mystery of who stabbed
不来聚会的负心汉凶手
Koothrappali in the back with the weapon of indifference,
就是你们几个
it was all of you.
我觉得这个不算是推理
I don't think that qualifies as a mystery.
因为我们都知道了啊
We all knew what we were doing.
我们很抱歉 Rajesh
We're sorry, Rajesh.
要不下周吧
Maybe we can do it next week.
等等 这补偿有点太过了吧
Whoa, whoa, we're not that sorry.
别担心了 我知道你们不喜欢
Don't worry, I can take a hint.
不会有什么杀人解密聚会了
No more murder mystery parties.
- 太好了  - 哈利路亚
- Great. Thank you.  - Hallelujah.
因为我想了一个更好的主意
Because I've got something even better planned.
- 噢不! 搞啥啊?  - 别啊
- Aw! Why?  - Come on.
你们先听着
Just hear me out.
我决定让你们参加
I'm going to make you guys
一个寻宝游戏 就像麻省理工他们举办的那个
a scavenger hunt like they have at M.I.T.
嗯...
Oh...
那不错
I loved those.
当时我们每年都玩这个
I did them every year there.
我们普林斯顿也玩这个
We did them at Princeton, too.
哦 真好
Oh, that's cute.
听起来普大像一流大学似的(嘲讽Leonard母校)
Like it's a real college.
真好玩... 我本来打算黑麻省理工的(嘲讽Howard母校)
That's amusing... I was going to say that about M.I.T.,
不过黑普林斯顿也行
but it works for Princeton, too.
哈佛的寻宝游戏很难
Scavenger hunts at Harvard were really tough.
我每次第一步就被卡住了...
I always got stuck on the first challenge...
那就是找个队友都找不到
trying to find someone to be on a team with me.
好吧 这是个悲伤的故事
I guess that story's more sad than funny.
我喜欢寻宝游戏
I love scavenger hunts.
我经常和朋友去玩
My friends and I had them all the time.
我们说的可能不太一样
Oh, these are a little different.
顶尖的几所名校都有一个传统
There's a tradition at elite universities.
普林斯顿也有
And Princeton.
一个通过解谜题
A tradition of hunts
来寻找宝物的游戏 解谜需要用到
full of puzzles that rely on logic
逻辑 科学和一些偏门知识
and obscure knowledge, science.
我们就是在城里乱逛
Oh, in ours we would just run around town looking for a store
然后找酒喝
that would sell us beer.
那么 谁参加?
So, uh, who's in?
- 我觉得应该很有意思  - 恩 我也来
- I think it sounds fun.  - Yeah, me, too.
- 我玩  - 搞起来
- I'm in.  - Let's do it.
等下 我们是真的要玩
I'm sorry. Are we really doing this
还是跟上次聚会一样
or are we tricking Koothrappali again
耍Koothrappali玩玩的?
like with the dinner party?
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state *
* 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The Earth began to cool *
* 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools *
* 我们建长城 我们建金字塔 *
* We built the Wall We built the pyramids *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
* That all started with a big bang *
生活大爆炸 第七季第三集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调：初见
时间轴：pisces夜
翻译：期中求A+ 影子打酱油 捞盐要拨开大雾 初见
校对：UU这周没有due
装的啥?
What's all this?
为了赢得寻宝游戏
Oh, everything I could possibly need
所需要的道具
to win the scavenger hunt.
你真以为他会把我们带去保龄球场?
You really think he's gonna send us to a bowling alley?
如果去的话
Well, if he does,
你知道那儿的保龄球有多脏吗?
do you know how filthy those rental balls are?
简直是让我伸进去
They might as well stand on the corner
做直肠检查
and give away free rectal exams.
好了 大家注意
Okay, everybody.
你们准备好...
Who's ready for a...
去寻宝了吗?
scavenger hunt?
在这个...
Somewhere...
Pasadena城市某处
in the city of Pasadena,
我藏着
I've hidden
一枚金币
a golden coin.
哦!
Oh!
你们将会遇到十个
You will be faced with a total
难解的谜题!
of ten puzzles!
每个 咳...
Each p...
每个...
Each...
谜题都会指引你们
each puzzle will lead you
去下一个地点
to the location of the next.
最后一个谜题
The last of which
则会指出宝藏的地点
will lead you to the coin.
第一个发现宝藏的队伍...
The first team that finds it...
胜利!
wins!
一身的表演细胞啊
He is a born showman.
有问题吗?
Any questions?
我有 为了公平
Yes, to be fair, do people
要不要让一下普林斯顿的? (嘲讽Leonard)
who went to Princeton get a head start?
这不好笑
That's not funny.
你听懂之后 就会觉得好笑了
Oh, it actually is if you get the joke.
这个讽刺的梗是
It's based on the premise
普林斯顿不是一所好学校
that Princeton isn't a very good school.
哈 哈
Ha-ha.
瞧? 现在他懂了
Oh, see? Now he gets it.
好了 开始吧
Okay, guys, go ahead
分成两个组
and divide yourselves into teams of two.
情侣组队?
Should we just do couples?
情侣可以
Couples sounds great.
也可以试试抽签
Or we could mix things up.
从帽子里抽名字
Maybe pick names out of a hat.
随便了
Whatever.
等等...
Whoa, whoa...
等下
whoa.
你为啥就不承认
Why don't you just admit
你不想和我一队呢
you don't want to be on a team with me.
我说了"情侣组队也不错"
I just said, "Couples sound great."
我知道了 你认为我是笨蛋
Mm-hmm, yeah, you don't think I'm smart enough.
觉得我是个累赘
You think I'm gonna be a liability.
尽管我说话还用了
Even though I totally just used
"累赘"这种高级词汇
the word "liability" correctly
还用对了
in a sentence.
用对了
Yeah.
好吧 那就... 那就情侣吧
All right, let's... let's do couples.
我想和你一队
I want to.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
我们随机组队
Let's mix things up.
我和Sheldon一队 把你打得屁滚尿流!
I choose Sheldon, and we're gonna kick your ass!
嗯... 真的吗?
Yeah... really?
我第一次组队就得
The only time I'm ever picked first for a team
带着个累赘?
and I'm stuck with the liability?
别这么说 Penny才不是累赘
Stop that. Penny is not a liability.
谢谢 你想和我组队吗?
Thank you. Do you want to be on my team?
我们还是随机抽名字吧
Maybe we pick names out of a hat.
好了 快点把门关上
All right, hurry up and close the door
别让他们听到了
so they can't hear us.
你能别撅嘴了吗?
Would you stop pouting?
是你自己抽到我的
So, you picked my name.
别纠结了
Get over it.
没错 你知道我要抽到你
Yes, and do you know what the odds are
有多难吗?
I'd pick your name?
不知道
No.
还挺难的... 五分之一呢
It's not hard... one in five.
现在你知道我干嘛要撅嘴了
Now you know why I'm pouting.
各小组注意
All right, teams.
准备好打开第一个谜题
Get ready to open your first puzzle.
开始!
Go!
看到我的良苦用心了吗?
Do you see what I did?
第一道谜题就是拼图!
The first puzzle is a puzzle!
天啊 多可爱啊
Oh, my God, how adorable is that?
我真希望我有个像我一样的朋友
I wish I had a friend like me.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
拼图得从边框开始
You have to start with the edges.
拼图又没有定则 Sheldon
Well, there's no right way, Sheldon.
我已经找到几块能拼在一起的了
I already found a few pieces that fit.
没错 那就拆了它们 从边框开始拼
Yeah, well, take them apart and start with the edges.
别再浪费时间了
And stop wasting time.
你拼图技术真不错
Wow, you're really good at puzzles.
我小时候经常拼
I did them all the time as a kid.
我妈妈说
As my mom used to say,
"当你拼图的时候
"When you're doing a puzzle,
感觉就像是有一千个小伙伴"
it's like having a thousand friends."
她总是说这样有趣的谎言
She was full of fun lies like that.
比较一下 你会好受点
If it makes you feel any better,
我妈只会吃油腻的蛋糕
my mom's just full of pound cake.
很抱歉 你得跟我一组
I'm sorry you got stuck with me.
我猜你肯定很想和Bernadette一组
I bet you wanted to be with Bernadette.
你和Bernadette一起玩过游戏吗?
Have you ever played a game with Bernadette?
没有
No.
你有没有和狼人一起
Have you ever gone
被关在铁笼子里过?
into a steel cage with a wolverine?
快点 快点 快点!
Faster, faster, faster!
你听得懂吗?
Do you not know that word?
就是"再快点"!
It means "more fast"!
别对我大吼大叫
Stop yelling at me.
嘿!
Hey!
我这可不算大吼大叫
You'll know when I'm yelling at you.
噢 是漫画书店!
Ooh, ooh, it's the comic book store!
好了 我们走吧
All right, come on.
我们得去那儿
That's where we have to go.
但我们还没拼完图
But we haven't finished the puzzle.
这... 这又没关系!
Well, it... it doesn't matter!
我们知道答案了!
We know the answer!
得了吧 你自以为知道了答案
Come on. You think you know the answer.
说不定这是个陷阱
But it could be a trick.
万一等拼完图
What if when the puzzle's complete,
发现窗玻璃上有个标志写着
there's a sign in the window that says,
"去卖小火车的店"?
"Go to the train store"?
根本不会有这样的标志
Okay, it's not gonna say that.
我希望你错了
Well, I hope you're wrong.
因为我真的很想去卖小火车的店
I really want to go to the train store.
是漫画书店
It's the comic book store.
我们走!
Let's go!
快点 蠢货 是漫画书店!
Come on, numb nuts, it's the comic book store!
是漫画书店 就是漫画书店
It's the comic book store, it's the comic book store,
肯定是漫画书店!
it's the comic book store!
的确是漫画书店
It's the comic book store.
你觉得Penny在生我的气吗?
Do you think Penny's mad at me?
因为你在右车道
Because you're in the right lane
前面有辆公交车 你却不超车?
behind a bus and you won't go around it?
她肯定觉得这很迷人
I'm sure she finds it charming.
不是 因为我不想和她一组
No, because I didn't want her on my team.
我开始觉得她闪过了一枚子弹
I'm starting to think she dodged a bullet.
还是世界上最慢的子弹
The slowest bullet in the world.
天啊 我从来都不知道你那么好斗
Geez, I never realized you were so competitive.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
可能... 是因为我和
It's... it's probably because I grew up
五个兄弟姐妹一起长大
with five brothers and sisters
所以我得为每个...
so I had to fight for every...
天啊 刚才有鸟飞过 你竟然踩刹车!
Oh, my God, you did not just slow down for a bird!
它们会飞的 懂吗?!
You know they fly, right?!
我觉得这是第一次
I think this is the first time we've ever
我们俩单独在一起
actually been alone together.
我猜你说对了
Huh, I guess you're right.
这是什么原因呢?
Wonder why that is?
要我说 最有可能是因为除了交际圈
Well, off the top of my head, I'd say we don't have a lot
我们没什么共同点
in common except for the people we're involved with.
再加上我们刚认识的时候 Penny警告我
Plus, when we first met, Penny warned me never
别单独上你的车
to get into a car alone with you.
这样啊
Yeah.
我猜我们的共同点比想象中的多
You know, I bet you and I have more in common than we think.
比如?
Such as?
我不知道
I don't know.
跟我说说你喜欢什么
Tell me some things you like.
我想想
Uh, let's see.
我喜欢竖琴 "普雷里的小屋"
I like harps, Little House on the Prairie,
中世纪诗词 中世纪文学...
medieval poetry, medieval literature...
要不还是听听音乐吧?
Hey, how about some music?
好啊
Great.
Sheldon从来不让我在车里听音乐
Sheldon never lets me listen to music in the car.
他不想别人觉得他是黑社会的
He doesn't want to be mistaken for a gang member.
找点你喜欢的歌
Find something you like.
披头士的 太无聊
Beatles, boring.
阿姆的 太疯狂
Eminem, scary.
艾尔・扬科维奇?
Weird Al?
著名歌曲恶搞专家
你到底多大啊?
How old are you?
尼尔・戴蒙德?
Neil Diamond?
没错 我爱尼尔・戴蒙德
Yeah, I love Neil Diamond.
我也爱尼尔・戴蒙德
I love Neil Diamond.
# 甜美的卡洛琳 #
# Sweet Caroline #
# 嘣 吧 哒 #
# Bum-ba-da #
# 美好时光总是那么棒 #
# Good times never seemed so good #
# 那么棒 那么棒 那么棒 #
# So good, so good, so good #
嘿 谢谢你愿意把店借给我
Oh, hey, thanks for letting me use
做寻宝游戏的场地
the comic book store as part of the scavenger hunt.
不用客气
Oh, my pleasure.
我特别乐意帮忙组织这些
Always happy to help out with fun things
我没被邀请的有趣活动
that I wasn't invited to be a part of.
恭喜
Oh, congratulations.
你们是第一支到达的队伍
You're the first team to arrive.
太棒了! 别小看我
Yes! It's not a ruse to make fun of me.
这场游戏我赢定了!
It's a real game and I'm winning it!
下一个谜题是个谜语
Your next puzzle is a riddle.
还是由"谜题大师"
And who better to give it to you
来揭晓谜语吧
than The Riddler?
快点 快点 快点
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
快点 快点 快点!
go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
你怎么跑得比我还慢?
How am I faster than you?
我穿着高跟鞋 还停下来接了个电话
I'm wearing heels and I stopped to take a phone call.
我有哮喘
I have asthma.
滚开!
Back off!
"请你猜猜我的谜
"Riddle me this.
啊哟 啊哟 快来围观
Arrah, Arrah, and gather round,
他隶属于超级英雄军团
the work of this hero is legion-bound.
他的数字乘以N
He multiplies N by the number of He,
此物便在屋中寻"
and in this room the thing you'll see."
- 写得不错吧?  - 是啊
- Good riddle, huh?  - Yeah.
所以说 你们商量玩什么的时候
So when you guys plan fun activities,
是不是压根就...
does my name even...
没想起我来 还是...?
come up, or...?
我邀请过你参加我的杀人解密聚会
I invited you to my murder mystery party.
你才没有
No, you didn't.
噢
Oh.
我们是最后一组到的 动作快啊!
We're the last ones here, hurry up!
这是马拉松 又不是百米冲刺
It is a marathon, not a sprint.
马拉松也是要跑的啊!
People run in a marathon!
人家可没背着个保龄球跑马拉松
Not with a bowling ball on their back.
嘿 Penny 我只想说 祝好运
Hey, Penny, I just wanted to say good luck,
希望你别记恨我
and I hope there's no hard feelings.
嘿 罗密欧同学!
Hey, Romeo!
用你自己的时间修复感情去
Repair your relationship on your own time.
放轻松嘛 这个谜有难度
Relax, it's a hard puzzle.
得一会儿才解得开
It's gonna take a while to solve.
- "请你猜猜我的谜..."  - 搞定
- "Riddle me this..."  - Got it.
嘿 普林斯顿小子 瞧瞧看
Hey, Princeton, look at that,
社区学院的夜校队可是遥遥领先了噢
Team Community College Night School is in the lead.
我还以为咱们叫闪电鲨二人组呢
I thought we were the Lightning Sharks.
嘿 你觉得这个是不是...
Hey, you know what this could mean...
哦 哦 说得好
Oh, oh, that's good.
那这个就是...
Then this would be...
没错了
That's it.
去我们的Neil小车车咯!
To the Neil Mobile!
我就知道 咱们输定了!
I knew it, we're gonna lose!
等等 我知道了 我想出来了!
Wait, I got it. I got it!
那真是要给你发去贺电了 末班车同学
Congratulations, you got it last.
你真的好凶 你知不知道?
You're really mean, you know that?
原来没一个是来买东西的
So no one's gonna buy anything.
啊哈!
Aha!
很好...
Okay...
看看
Let's see.
"为了进入下一关
"To continue on your quest,
水落石出是王道"
leave no stone unturned."
哦
Ooh.
下一条线索一定藏在
The next clue must be hidden
这边某块石头下面
under one of these rocks.
哦 好的
Oh. Okay.
Sheldon 我... 我还是忍不住要问
Sheldon, I... I've got to ask.
你怎么想出来是地质学实验室的?
How did you figure out that it was the geology lab?
哦 小菜一碟
Oh, simple.
谜语中的"啊哟 啊哟"说的是Jan Arrah
The "Arrah, Arrah" in the riddle meant Jan Arrah,
超级英雄军团中的一员
a member of the Legion of Superheroes,
人称元素小子
known as Element Lad.
而"他"这个词
And then the word "He",
并不是那个人称代词男他
it wasn't the masculine pronoun,
而是 "HE"
but rather, "H-E",
氦元素的缩写
the abbreviation for helium.
知道我意思了吗?
See where I'm going with this?
知道
Yes.
装得真像
Nice try.
元素小子的超能力
Now, Element Lad's ability
是改变化学元素本身
is the power to transmute chemical elements.
氦的原子序数为2
Helium has an atomic number of two.
要是你拿2乘以"N"的原子序数...
If you multiply that by the atomic number of "N"...
也就是氮...
nitrogen...
得出14 原子序数14对应的元素是...?
you get 14, which is the atomic number of...?
逗你玩儿的 是硅
I'm just funnin' you, silicon.
而硅是地球表面
And that is the most common element
含量最丰富的元素
in the Earth's surface.
所以就把范围缩小到
So that narrowed it down
地质学实验室和化学实验室了
to the geology lab or the chemistry lab.
哇
Wow.
有什么了不起的 我能在水下喝啤酒
I can drink a beer underwater.
你父母想必异常骄傲
And I'm sure your parents are proud.
最后呢
Now, finally,
"此物便在屋中寻"这句
the line "in this room the thing you'll see"
明显是指
was an obvious reference
神奇四侠里的石头人
to Fantastic Four member The Thing,
全身都由...
who's made entirely of...
停
Shut up.
我想出来了
I solved it.
是地图坐标
Those are map coordinates.
记下了 走吧
Got 'em. Let's go.
等等
Well, wait.
你... 你不想知道我怎么想出来的吗?
D... Don't you want to know how I figured it out?
百事通注定孤独一生啊 Penny
No one likes a know-it-all, Penny.
# 在船上 在飞机上 #
# On the boats and on the planes #
# 他们要来美帝啦 #
# They're coming to America #
# 再也不要回头 #
# Never looking back again #
# 他们要来美帝啦... #
# They're coming to America... #
呃 你开我的车不要紧
Um, I'm okay with you driving my car.
可是不要飞我的车行不行
I'm not okay with you flying my car.
别担心 我老爸是条子 出了事他救咱们
Don't sweat it, my dad's a cop. He can fix things.
呃呵
Uh-huh.
死了也能救回来?
Like death?
也许你孩子是个三好学生
Your kid may be an honor student
不过你是个三级脑残!
but you're a moron!
Penny不回我短信
Penny's not answering my texts.
管它呢? 注意力放到游戏上
Who cares? Focus on the game.
就是因为这个蠢游戏 她才生我的气的
This stupid game is why she's mad in the first place.
我要告诉她我不玩了
I'm telling her I'm quitting.
不行!
No!
你要是考虑感情的话
Quitting would be the worst thing
最坏的就是你退出了
for your relationship.
为什么?
Why?
因为这会让她更加认定
Because it would make you seem like
你是那样的人
something she already thinks you are.
她认为我是什么样的人?
What does she think I am?
怎么说好呢?
How do I put this?
她一直都用某个女性部位
She's been known to call you a name
称呼你
that usually applies to a lady part.
或是猫
Or a cat.
或是爱哭鬼
Or a willow.
我不相信她居然这样说我
I can't believe she would say that about me.
你要是想哭的话
If you're gonna cry about it
我包里就有纸巾
there's tissues in my purse.
也许你自己包里也有
Unless you got some in yours.
大爱哭鬼
Big willow.
# 他们要来美帝啦 #
# They're coming to America #
# 此时此刻 #
# Today #
# 就在今天 #
# 今天 #
# Today #
# 今天! #
# Today! #
哦... 再开30尺
Okay... another 30 feet.
好吧
Okay.
哦
Oh.
是个保龄球馆
It's a bowling alley.
哦
Yes.
太棒了!
Yes!
我真是个旷世奇才!
My brain is better than everybody's!
# 把爱刻在石头上 #
# Love on the rocks #
# 那都不算什么 #
# Ain't no big surprise #
# 给我一杯酒 #
# Just pour me a drink #
# 谎话说出口... #
# And I'll tell you some lies... #
说我不是爷们
Call me a lady part.
我们走着瞧吧
We'll see about that.
拿到线索了吗?
Can you reach the clue?
差一点
Almost.
快点 保龄球馆里
Hurry, Sheldon and Penny
Sheldon和Penny就在我们后面
were right behind us in the bowling alley.
拿到了!
Got it!
太棒了 爬上来吧
Great,climb back up.
快点!
Come on!
Penny有可能说对了
Yeah, Penny might be onto something.
去天文馆!
To the planetarium!
走起!
Let's go!
著名化石遗址 也是个博物馆
去沥青坑!
To the tar pits!
走起!
Let's go!
下个月有尼尔・戴蒙德的演唱会!
There's a Neil Diamond concert next month!
走起!
Let's go!
三个袋子 都没打开
Three bags, no one's opened 'em.
我们是最先到达的!
We're the first ones here!
- 是脏衣服 交给你了  - 什么?
- It's dirty laundry. You're up.  - What? You...
干嘛给我?
Why me?
因为你一辈子都在
Because you've been training
训练自己
for this your whole life.
怎样在脏衣服堆里生存
You live in a pile of dirty laundry.
他们已经到了
They're here first.
就怪你让我给那个盲人让路 我才慢下来的
This is because you made me slow down for that blind guy.
好了 线索一定藏在袋子里
Okay, the clue must be in the bag.
线索一定藏在袋子里
The clue must be in the bag.
这... 这只有几条裤子
What's... it's just a bunch of pants.
这只有几条裤子
It's just a bunch of pants.
真不敢相信
You know, I'm surprised
你竟然抄我的答案
you want to copy my answers
你看 我都不够格和你一组
since I'm not even smart enough to be on your team.
你为什么非要和一个
Well, why would you want to be on someone's team
你叫他...
who you like to call a...
我都不好意思在Sheldon面前说出这个词
I can't even say it in front of Sheldon.
你什么意思啊?
What are you talking about?
你知道我什么意思
You know exactly what I'm talking about.
她不知道
No, she doesn't.
这都是我编的
I just made that up.
你为什么要编这个?
Why would you do that?
因为你要放弃了 像个...
Because you were about to quit like a big...
Sheldon 捂住耳朵
Sheldon, cover your ears.
我不是小朋友了
I'm not a child.
我知道"傻瓜"这个词
I know the word "ninny."
你还是早认输为好
Yeah, well, you should have quit
要不然我会把你打的满地找牙的
'cause I'm still gonna beat your ass.
真希望我们队也有个这样的汉子
Wish I had a man like her on my team.
我... 我和Penny
Hey, I... I am every bit
一样是个真汉子
as much of a man as Penny.
开始吧!
Now, let's do this!
等等 不全是裤子 有一件T恤衫
Wait, it's not all pants, there's one shirt.
哦
Oh.
嘿 这是我的T恤衫
Hey, that's my shirt.
- 这件也是  - 不 那件可不是我的
- This one is, too.  - No, no, that's not mine.
上面有个大污点
That has a big spot on it.
看看这个
But wait.
也有个大污点
So does this one.
也许这个点就是线索
Maybe the spot's the clue.
"Sheldon的点儿"
"Sheldon's spot."
金币藏在你的专座下!
The coin is in your spot!
哦 好机智
Oh, that's clever.
快点!
Hurry!
马上就来
Be there in a minute.
我先用洗衣液泡上!
I just have to pre-soak these!
拦住她 Leonard! 拦住她!
Stop her, Leonard! Stop her!
金币到底在哪里?
Well, where the hell's the coin?
难道不是Sheldon的专座吗?
Wasn't the answer Sheldon's spot?
你说对了 Leonard
Oh, yes, Leonard.
金币本来在这儿
Yes, it was.
那它现在哪去了?
Then where's the coin?
对啊
Yes, exactly.
现在哪去了?
Where is the coin?
为什么不看一下你们的口袋呢?
Why don't you look in your pockets?
早些时候我悄悄放进去的
I slipped them in there earlier today.
我不懂
I don't get it.
有什么不懂的?
Don't you see?
我们一起享受了快乐时光
When we're all having fun together,
这就是胜利
we're already winners.
等下
Oh, look.
看见没?
See?
我也赢了
Even I'm a winner.
你玩我们呢吧?
Are you kidding me?
这是我见过最蠢的事情了
That is the stupidest thing I've ever heard.
你烂透了
You suck so hard.
我是想...
Well, I thought...
我不想让任何人
Come on, I didn't want anyone
因为输掉游戏而难过
to feel bad at the end of the game.
有些谜题又确实很难
And some of those puzzles were really hard
我也不知道谁会沦落到和Penny一组
and I didn't know who was gonna get Penny.
受死吧
Run.
好吧... 我刚不是那个意思
Okay, okay, that... that came out wrong,
你们得承认
but you have to admit,
大家玩得很开心
you all had a wonderful time.
快躲回印度吧
Run to India.
我只是想做件好事!
I just wanted to do something beautiful!
看啊
Hey, look.
我赢了
I won.
# 嘿 她触动了我的小心脏 #
# Hey, she got the way to move me, #
# 雪莉 #
# Cherry #
# 她和我心意相通 #
# She got the way to groove me, #
# 雪莉 宝贝 #
# Cherry, baby. #
# 她触动了我的小心脏 #
# She got the way to move me. #
# 她和我心意相通 #
# She got the way to groove me. #
# 她触动了我的小心脏 #
# She got the way to move me, #
# 雪莉 #
# Cherry. #
# 她和我心意相通 #
# She got the way to groove me. #
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/==--
协调：初见
时间轴：pisces夜
翻译：期中求A+ 影子打酱油 捞盐要拨开大雾 初见
校对：UU这周没有due